<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="desc">Snape arrives to apprehend Black but is knocked out by Harry Disarming spell. Lupin and Black reveal that Scabbers is actually the Animagus form of Pettigrew, who betrayed Harrys parents, faked his death and framed Black for his own crimes. Turning Pettigrew back into human form, the group head back to the castle, but the full moon causes Lupin to transform and Pettigrew escapes. Black transforms into his animal form and fights off werewolf Lupin, who seriously injures Black. Black manages to escape when a distant wolf cry distracts Lupin and sends him off. Harry finds Black, who are then both attacked by Dementors until an unseen figure casts a powerful Patronus charm to ward them off. Harry falls unconscious, awakening in the infirmary with Dumbledore and Hermione. Snape arrives to apprehend Black but is knocked out by Harry Disarming spell. Lupin and Black reveal that Scabbers is actually the Animagus form of Pettigrew, who betrayed Harrys parents, faked his death and framed Black for his own crimes. Turning Pettigrew back into human form, the group head back to the castle, but the full moon causes Lupin to transform and Pettigrew escapes. Black transforms into his animal form and fights off werewolf Lupin, who seriously injures Black. Black manages to escape when a distant wolf cry distracts Lupin and sends him off. Harry finds Black, who are then both attacked by Dementors until an unseen figure casts a powerful Patronus charm to ward them off. Harry falls unconscious, awakening in the infirmary with Dumbledore and Hermione. Snape arrives to apprehend Black but is knocked out by Harry Disarming spell. Lupin and Black reveal that Scabbers is actually the Animagus form of Pettigrew, who betrayed Harrys parents, faked his death and framed Black for his own crimes. Turning Pettigrew back into human form, the group head back to the castle, but the full moon causes Lupin to transform and Pettigrew escapes. Black transforms into his animal form and fights off werewolf Lupin, who seriously injures Black. Black manages to escape when a distant wolf cry distracts Lupin and sends him off. Harry finds Black, who are then both attacked by Dementors until an unseen figure casts a powerful Patronus charm to ward them off. Harry falls unconscious, awakening in the infirmary with Dumbledore and Hermione.</string>
<!--    <item name="article_heading" type="id">article_heading</item>-->
<!--    <item name="article_subheading" type="id">articlesubheading</item>-->
<!--    <item name="article" type="id">article</item>-->
</resources>